[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of person is described by the expression green around the gills?", "correct_answer": "Physically ill", "incorrect_answers": ["New at fishing", "Gardner novice", "Jealous over someone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sanaa Lathan starred in all the three movies from the Blade trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie can the following conversation be heard? \nSir Leigh Teabing: And this is from the gospel of Mary Magdalene herself. \nSophie Neveu: She wrote a gospel? \nRobert Langdon: She may have.", "correct_answer": "The Da Vinci Code", "incorrect_answers": ["Angels and Demons", "Passion of Christ", "The Seventh Sign"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many muscles are in your face?", "correct_answer": "30", "incorrect_answers": ["44", "12", "8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of drink is the traditional Native American beverage called Champurrado?", "correct_answer": "Chocolate drink", "incorrect_answers": ["Beer", "Coca tea", "A type of tequila"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first time traveler in the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Einstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Marty", "Doc", "Marty and Doc"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name all the Scandinavian countries.", "correct_answer": "Sweden, Denmark, Norway, Iceland", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden, Norway, Denmark, Finland, Iceland, Lithuania", "Sweden, Denmark, Norway, Finland", "Sweden, Denmark, Norway, Finland, Iceland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country has the most full sized breweries:", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["The USA", "Belgium", "The UK"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the wolfs scientific name Canis lupus pallipes?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During this battle, which took place towards the end of the American Revolutionary War, Lincoln had to surrender along with 3000 troops.", "correct_answer": "Charleston", "incorrect_answers": ["Stroudsburg", "Valley Forge", "Baltimore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Pedro give to Summer to convince her to go to the dance with him in the movie Napoleon Dynamite?", "correct_answer": "a cake", "incorrect_answers": ["bracelet", "flowers and candy", "a Mexican pinata"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Captain Quints first mate on the Orca?", "correct_answer": "Matt Hooper", "incorrect_answers": ["David Brown", "Richard Zanuck", "Carl Gottlieb"]}]